PATRICIA O'NEILL

Junior Full Stack Developer

Athlone, Co.Westmeath · 0852164132

pattytonyoneill@gmail.com · https://www.linkedin.com/in/patricia-o-neill-71a286217 · github.com/pattytonyoneill

Junior Full Stack Developer recently graduated from Code Institute. Experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Django, Full Stack Framework & Ecommerce Applications. My skills are that I am organized, a leader, can work in a team or as an individual. Also am a good communicator with problem solving skills.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

JULY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2022

DIPLOMA IN SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT (E-COMMERCE APPLICATIONS), CODE INSTITUTE

SEPTEMBER 1986 - MAY 1990

BACHELOR OF ARTS PSYCHOLOGY, MINOR IN COMPUTERS, COLLEGE OF SAINT ELIZABETH

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

MACGABBEN ARCHEOLOGICAL, WEBSITE FOR AN ARCHEOLOGICAL COMPANY

GITHUB – https://github.com/pattytonyoneill/archeology-company

Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, Github, Gitpod

FAMILY GAMESHOW, GAME APP DEPLOYED TO HEROKU, QUIZ FOR THE FAMILY TOPICS

INCLUDE: HARRY POTTER, STAR TREK, MARVEL AND DISNEY

GITHUB – https://github.com/pattytonyoneill/familygameshow

Technologies Used: Python, Github, Gitpod

HANGMAN, GAME APP DEPLOYED TO HEROKU,

CLASSIC HANGMAN GAME

GITHUB - https://github.com/pattytonyoneill/hangman

Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, Heroku, Github, Gitpod

OUR FAMILY RECIPES, FAMILY RECIPES APP DEPLOYED TO HEROKU, FAMILY RECIPES THAT CAN EASILY ACCESSED BY FAMILY & FRIENDS

GITHUB - https://github.com/pattytonyoneill/FamilyRecipes

Technologies Used: Python, Django, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, Heroku, Cloudinary, Github, **Gitpod**

CAITLIN'S CRAFTS, CRAFTS WEBSITE APP DEPLOYED TO HEROKU USING AWS & STRIPE FOR

PAYMENTS, CRAFTS WEBSITE FOR SELLING HOMEMADE CRAFTS

GITHUB - https://github.com/pattytonyoneill/caitlins crafts

Technologies Used: Python, Django, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, Heroku, Cloudinary, Github,

Gitpod, Stripe, AWS

WORK EXPERIENCE

1995-PRESENT

CARER, CARED FOR FAMILY MEMBER WITH SPECIAL NEEDS

ARRANGED APPOINTMENTS, HOMESCHOOLED HER FOR HIGH SCHOOL IN THE UNITED STATES, TOOK HER TO SPEECH THERAPY AND OCCUPATIONAL THERAPY APPOINTMENTS AND TOOK CARE OF ADMINISTERING MEDICINE WHEN NEEDED.

1992 - 1994

SECRETARY, CANADA DRY BOTTLING COMPANY

IN CHARGE OF INVENTORY, BILLING AND PHONE ORDERS.

1990 – 1992

RACK CLERK, SHOWBOAT HOTEL CASINO & SPA

STARTED GUEST SERVICES MOVED TO CHECKIN DESK & RACK CLERK.
RESPONSIBILITIES: VIP CHECK IN & CUT KEYS. ALSO HANDLED CHECK IN FOR BUS
AND TOUR GROUPS AND DISTRUSTING THEIR KEYS.

ADDITIONAL LEARNING

CODEACADEMY, USED WEBSITE PRIOR TO SIGNING UP TO CODE INSTITUTE TO GIVE ME A BASE KNOWLEDGE AND TO REVIEW KNOWLEDGE, STUDIED: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

LANGUAGES: FLUENT ENGLISH/BEGINNER SPANISH